RG 079:001, Department of Environmental Protection: Central Office
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. Commissioner, 1957-2004
  - Stanley J. Pac, 1973-1987
    - Subject Files, 1973-1980; 1988-024 (part)
      - Hazardous Materials Management, 1979 May-1979 October (Box 13-8)
      - Hazardous Materials Management, 1978 February-1979 April (Box 13-1)
      - Hazardous Materials Management Unit, 1980 June-1980 December (Box 13-1)
      - Hazardous Waste Management Task Force, 1980 January-1980 October (Box 13-1)
      - Hazardous Waste Siting Council, 1980 January-1980 October (Box 13-1)
      - State of Connecticut Health Department (Box 13-1)
      - Hearts and Flowers, 1977 January-1980 December (Box 13-1)
      - Heritage Task Force (Box 13-1)
      - Heritage Conservation and Recreation Service, 1978 January-1980 October (Box 13-1)
      - Heritage Conservation and Recreation Service, 1980 March-1980 December (Box 13-1)
      - Housatonic River Commission (Box 13-1)
      - CL&P Housatonic Project (Box 13-1)
      - Helco Housatonic Project (Box 13-1)
      - Housatonic River Study (Box 13-1)
      - Housatonic River Treatment Plant, 1979 May-1980 January (Box 13-1)
      - Commissioner Stanley Pac (Box 13-1)
      - State of Connecticut-Department of Housing, 1980 December (Box 13-1)
      - Commission on Human Rights and opportunities, 1976 March-1980 August (Box 13-1)
      - Hunting and Trapping- Wildlife, 1978 October-1980 December (Box 13-1)
      - Hydropower (Box 13-1)
      - Indian Affairs, 1976 January-1977 November (Box 13-1)
      - Indian Affairs, 1978 January-1980 September (Box 13-1)
      - Indirect Source Air Compliance-Letters and Memos (Box 13-1)
      - Inland Wetlands, 1977 July-1978 December (Box 13-1)
      - Inland Wetlands, 1979 January-1980 September (Box 13-1)
      - Inspection and Maintenance, 1979 January-1979 December (Box 13-1)
      - Inspection and Maintenance, 1978 March-1978 November (Box 13-19)
      - Inspection and Maintenance, 1978 January-1978 February (Box 13-19)
      - Inspection and Maintenance, 1975 February-1977 December (Box 13-19)
      - Insulation- Urea Formaldehyde, 1977 December-1977 November (Box 13-19)
      - Insulation- Urea Formaldehyde, 1979 February-1979 December (Box 13-19)
      - Insulation- Urea Formaldehyde, 1980 January-1980 December (Box 13-19)
      - International Snowmobile Industry Association, 1976 May-1977 March (Box 13-19)
      - I-84 Eastern Connecticut (Box 13-19)
      - I-291 Farmington to Rocky Hill, 1976 December-1980 October (Box 13-19)
      - Interstate Highways, 1978 June-1980 November (Box 13-19)
      - Interstate Sanitation Commission, 1977 January-1980 August (Box 13-19)
      - Invitations, 1979 December+1980 May-1980 December (Box 13-19)
      - Ivy Mountain Farm - Goshen, 1977 January (Box 13-19)
      - John’s River Ride, 1979 December+1980 December (Box 13-19)
      - Labor, State Department of, 1978 January-1979 October (Box 13-19)
      - Lake Beeseck, 1977 March-1979 September (Box 13-19)
      - Lake Waramuag, 1977 January-1980 May (Box 13-19)
      - Lake Wonoscopomuc- Hypolimnetic Drawoff (Box 13-19)
      - Lakes Management, 1977 March-1979 September (Box 13-19)
      - Lakes- Twin Lakes Project, 1978 February-1978 June (Box 13-19)
      - Land Acquisition (SS Division), 1976 January-1980 September (Box 13-19)
      - Land and Water Conservation Fund, 1976 May-1980 December (Box 13-19)
      - Landfills, 1978 June-1978 November (Box 13-19)
      - Law Enforcement (C+P Division), 1977 March-1980 September (Box 13-19)
      - League of Women Voters, 1978 November-1980 September (Box 13-2)
      - Leesville Dam, 1977 November-1980 August (Box 13-2)
      - Legislation, 1976 February-1980 August (Box 13-2)
      - Legislative Program Review & Investigations Committee, 1975 July-1976 October (Box 13-2)
      - Licensing and Revenue, 1980 August-1981 December (Box 13-2)
      - Linear Park-Rte. 7 (Box 13-2)
      - Litter Control Unit, 1980 December (Box 13-2)
      - LIS-Dredging, Heritage Program, 1975 January-1976 October (Box 13-2)
      - Long Island Sound-Dredging, LISF Heritage Program, 1977 February-1979 December (Box 13-2)
      - Malls, 1977 May-1979 November (Box 13-2)
      - Management, 1978 May, 1980 January, 1980 June (Box 13-2)
      - Management Incentive Plan, 1978 September-1979 June (Box 13-2)
      - Mattabassett, 1980 March-1980 December (Box 13-2)
      - Milford, 1976 March-1980 October (Box 13-2)
      - Motor Vehicle, State Dept. of, 1977 January-1980 July (Box 13-2)
      - National Governors Conference, 1977 February-1977 August (Box 13-2)
      - National Hurricane Conference, 1980 March (Box 13-2)
      - Natural Resources Center, 1974-1978 April (Box 13-2)
      - Natural Resources Center, 1978 June-1979 April (Box 13-2)
      - Natural Resources Center, 1980 January-1980 October (Box 13-2)
      - Natural Resources Center, 1979 May-1979 October (Box 13-2)
      - New England Interstate Water Pollution Control Commission, 1977 January-1978 December (Box 13-2)
      - NERBC, 1976-1977 August (Box 13-2)
      - NERBC, 1977 September-1977 December (Box 13-9)
      - NERBC, 1979 January-1979 October (Box 13-9)
      - NERBC, 1979 November-1980 April (Box 13-9)
      - New England Regional Commission (Hazardous Waste), 1978 May-1980 March (Box 13-9)
      - News Releases, 1977 February-1980 October (Box 13-9)
      - Newspaper Clippings Various Dates, 1977-1982 (Box 13-9)
      - NPDES - National Pollution Discharge Elimination System, 1980 June (Box 13-9)
      - Noise Control Unit - DEP, 1970 December-1980 December (Box 13-9)
      - Norfolk, CT. - Town of, 1977 January-1977 December (Box 13-9)
      - North Haven Mall (Box 13-9)
      - Northeast Utilities Response to PFEC Questions, 1977 October 24 (Box 13-9)
      - Northeast Utilities, 1977 December-1980 July (Box 13-9)
      - Northeast Utilities, 1976 November-1977 September (Box 13-9)
      - Northeast Utilities Report on Strontium- 90 Levels in CT. Milk, 1977 September (Box 13-9)
      - Northeast Utilities Stability Analysis Docket #12 (Box 13-9)
      - Northeast Utilities Exhibit “R” (Bantam Lake), 1977 November-1980 August (Box 13-9)
      - Environmental Operating Report - Haddam Neck, 1975 January 1-1975 December 31 (Box 13-18)
      - Environmental Operating Report - Haddam Neck, 1977 January 1-1977 December 31 (Box 13-18)
      - Environmental Operating Report - Millstone, 1975 June 1-1975 December 31 (Box 13-18)
      - Environmental Operating Report - Millstone, 1977 January 1-1977 December 31 (Box 13-18)
      - Northeast Utilities Exhibit “R” Bantam Lake, 1980 August (Box 13-18)
      - Northeast Utilities Exhibit “R&W” (Box 13-18)
      - Norwalk, 1977 January-1980 December (Box 13-18)
      - Norwalk Harbor, 1977 April-1980 February (Box 13-18)
      - Norwich - Norwichtown, 1980 March-1980 September (Box 13-18)
      - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 1979 January-1980 December (Box 13-18)
      - Physical Protection of Plants and Materials, 1977 March (Box 13-18)
      - Purcell Report Critique - Bantam Lake (Box 13-18)
      - Oil + Chemical Spills Section, 1978 January-1980 October (Box 13-12)
      - Oil- Outer Continental Shelf, 1977 January-1980 October (Box 13-12)
      - Old Lyme Beach Association, 1977 July-1979 March (Box 13-12)
      - Old Saybrook, 1980 October-1980 November (Box 13-12)
      - Open Burning (Air Compliance), 1977 January-1980 June (Box 13-12)
      - Open Space Acquisition, 1975 May-1977 December (Box 13-12)
      - Open Space Acquisition, 1978 February-1980 August (Box 13-12)
      - Open Space Acquisition Request for Bond Funds, 1977 January-1980 February (Box 13-12)
      - Overtime, 1979 December-1980 December (Box 13-12)
      - PCB, 1979 (Box 13-12)
      - PCB, 1975+1978+1977 (Box 13-12)
      - PCB Housatonic, 1977 February-1979 December (Box 13-12)
      - PCB - State/EPA Agreement, 1977 August-1979 September (Box 13-12)
      - Permits Section (DEP) (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel - Adjudication’s, 1976 May-1980 October (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel- Administration (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel- Air Compliance Unit, 1976 April-1980 December (Box 13-12)
      - ACU Kennedy, Paula (Air) (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel- Asst. Attorney General (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel- Commissioners Office (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel- Complimentary, 1977 January-1980 December (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel- Conservation + Preservation, 1977 January-1980 October (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel- Employment Apps, 1977 January-1977 December (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel- Environmental Quality, Deputy Commissioner’s (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel- Financial Services (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel- Flextime Proposals (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel- Form 14 Tracking Sheets, 1977 November-1978 November (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel - Hazardous Materials Management Unit (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel- Information and Education (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel- Land Acquisition/Property Management (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel- Litter Control (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel- Management Analysis (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel- Masters Contracts (Box 13-12)
      - Personnel- Miscellaneous (Box 13-13)
      - Personnel- Natural Resource Center (Box 13-13)
      - Personnel- Noise Control Unit (Box 13-13)
      - Personnel- Parks and Recreation (Box 13-13)
      - Personnel- Personnel + Payroll (Box 13-13)
      - Personnel- Planning and Coordination/Coastal Area Management (Box 13-13)
      - Personnel- Purchasing and Central Services (Box 13-13)
      - Personnel- Radiation (Box 13-13)
      - Personnel- Resumes, 1979-1980 (Box 13-13)
      - Personnel- Resumes, 1977-1978 (Box 13-13)
      - Personnel- Retirement + Pension (Box 13-13)
      - Personnel- Senior Environmental Employee (Box 13-13)
      - Personnel- Solid Waste Unit (Box 13-13)
      - Personnel- Staff Services (Box 13-13)
      - Personnel- Water Compliance (Box 13-13)
      - Personnel- Water Resources (Box 13-13)
      - Personnel- Water + Related Resources (Box 13-13)
      - Pesticide Unit (Box 13-13)
      - Pesticide Unit, 1977-1978 (Box 13-13)
      - Pickett’s Pond Osbournedale St. Park (Box 13-13)
      - Plainfield, Town of (Box 13-13)
      - DEP Planning + Coordination (Box 13-13)
      - Planning and Development (C+P) (Box 13-13)
      - Comprehensive Outdoor Recreation Plan, 1974 December (Box 13-13)
      - Dept. of Planning and Energy Policy (Box 13-13)
      - Plymouth, Town of (Box 13-13)
      - Poultry Processing Plants Rytman and Kokoff (Box 13-13)
      - PFEC- Power Facilities Evaluation Council, 1977-1980 (Box 13-13)
      - PFEC (Box 13-13)
      - PFEC, 1977 November (Box 13-13)
      - Progress Reports to Governor (Box 13-13)
      - Property Management (Box 13-13)
      - PUCA Public Utilities Control Authority (Box 13-13)
      - Purchasing (DEP) (Box 13-14)
      - Quinnipiac Bridge (Box 13-14)
      - Radiation Control Unit, 1977, 1978 (Box 13-14)
      - Radiation Control Unit, 1979 (Box 13-14)
      - Radiation Control Unit, 1979 (Box 13-14)
      - Radiation Control Unit, 1980 (Box 13-14)
      - Radiation Control Unit, 1981 (Box 13-14)
      - Radiation Control Unit, 1981 (Box 13-14)
      - Railroad Advisory Task Force, 1979-1981 (Box 13-14)
      - Railroad Advisory Task Force, 1981 April-1981 December (Box 13-14)
      - Recycling (Box 13-14)
      - Redding, Town of (Box 13-14)
      - Rehabilitation Act, 1973 (Box 13-14)
      - Regulations (DEP) (Box 13-14)
      - Re-Organization (DEP), 1974 December-1977 August (Box 13-14)
      - Re-Organization (DEP), 1974 November-1977August (Box 13-6)
      - Re-Organization (DEP), 1977 August-1980 march (Box 13-6)
      - Resource Recovery, 1977 March-1981 November (Box 13-6)
      - Ride Sharing Program, 1976 April-1980 November (Box 13-6)
      - Rippowan Flood Control, 1978 November-1981 February (Box 13-6)
      - Ridgefield Sewage Treatment Plant, 1976 May-1980 December (Box 13-6)
      - Rocky Hill Landfill, 1977-1978 (Box 13-6)
      - Rocky Hill Landfill, 1978-1981 (Box 13-6)
      - Rocky Neck State Park, 1977 May-1981 September (Box 13-6)
      - Rooster River Flood Control, 1977 May-1981 August (Box 13-6)
      - Route 7 (Linear Park), 1975 September-1981 August (Box 13-6)
      - Route 25, 1977 (Box 13-6)
      - Route 72, 1977 February-1980 September (Box 13-6)
      - Roy Boe Bulkhead, 1976 July-1979 June (Box 13-6)
      - Rural Development Council, 1980 September-1981 January (Box 13-6)
      - Salisbury, Town of (Box 13-6)
      - Salmon River Flood Control, 1978 June-1980 October (Box 13-6)
      - Scantic River Restoration, 1978 June-1980 October (Box 13-6)
      - SCORP, 1978-1981 December (Box 13-6)
      - Security System, DAS Public Works, 1979 January-1978 January (Box 13-6)
      - See Program, Senior Environmental Employment Program (Box 13-6)
      - Selden Island, 1981 March-1981 August (Box 13-6)
      - Sewers, 1977 (Box 13-6)
      - Sewers, 1979-1981 (Box 13-4)
      - Shell beach (Box 13-4)
      - Sleeping Giant State Park (Box 13-4)
      - Sherwood Island State Park (Box 13-4)
      - Sick Leave (Box 13-4)
      - Soil Conservation Service (Box 13-4)
      - Solid Waste Management Advisory Council (Box 13-4)
      - CT. Solid Waste Mgt. Plan (Box 13-4)
      - Solid Waste, 1977 (Box 13-4)
      - Solid Waste, 1978 (Box 13-4)
      - Solid Waste, 1980+1981 (Box 13-4)
      - South Windham, Town of (Box 13-4)
      - Solvents Recovery-Southington (Box 13-4)
      - Somers, Town of (Box 13-4)
      - South Windsor, Town of (Box 13-4)
      - Southington, Town of (Box 13-4)
      - Space Requirements (Box 13-4)
      - Squantz Pond State Park (Box 13-4)
      - Staff Services (DEP) (Box 13-4)
      - Stamford, City of (Box 13-4)
      - Standardization Committee, 1979 (Box 13-4)
      - Standardization Committee, 1980 (Box 13-4)
      - Standardization (Box 13-4)
      - SIP State Implementation Plan, 1977 August-1979 February (Box 13-17)
      - SIP, 1979 March-1979 August (Box 13-17)
      - SIP, 1980 February-1980 September (Box 13-17)
      - SIP, 1980 September-1981 November (Box 13-17)
      - SIP RAC SIP Revision Advisory Committee (Box 13-17)
      - State Planning and Development Committee (Box 13-17)
      - State Science, Engineering & Technology Steering Committee (Box 13-17)
      - State Tree Protection Examining Board (Appointees) (Box 13-17)
      - State Owned Housing (Box 13-17)
      - Sterling, Town of (Box 13-17)
      - Stonington, Town of (Box 13-17)
      - Stratford, Town of (Box 13-17)
      - Structure of State Government (Preliminary Discussion Draft) 10/76, 1976 October (Box 13-17)
      - Suggestion Awards Program (Box 13-17)
      - Sulphur (High), 1976 January-1980 August (Box 13-17)
      - Sulphur (High), 1980 August-1980 December (Box 13-17)
      - Summer Employment (Box 13-17)
      - Talcott Mountain (Box 13-17)
      - Tashua Shopping Park (Trumbull) (Box 13-17)
      - Thames River Basin (Outfall) (Box 13-17)
      - Tidal Wetlands (Box 13-17)
      - Timber (Box 13-11)
      - Tire Disposal (Box 13-11)
      - Tolland, Town of (Box 13-11)
      - Tornado, 1979 October (Box 13-11)
      - Torrington, Town of (Box 13-11)
      - Trade Publications (Box 13-11)
      - Dept. of Transportation Proposed Transportation Control Plan, 1976 (Box 13-11)
      - Dept. of Transportation, 1975 April-1979 December (Box 13-11)
      - 1980 Master Transportation Plan (Box 13-11)
      - Dept. of Transportation, 1980 March-1981 June (Box 13-11)
      - Travel Authorization Requests (Box 13-11)
      - Tri-State Regional Planning Commission, 1976 August-1978 September (Box 13-11)
      - Tri- State Regional Planning commission, 1978 September-1981 February (Box 13-11)
      - Trout Brook Flood Control Project (Box 13-11)
      - Trumbull, Town of (Box 13-11)
      - Uncas Lake, Lyme, CT. (Box 13-11)
      - United Illuminating, 1979 March-1980 September (Box 13-11)
      - United Illuminating, 1980 October-1981 June (Box 13-11)
      - United Nuclear Corporation Project (Box 13-11)
      - University of Hartford Correction Institute (Box 13-11)
      - Urban Parks and Recreation (Box 13-11)
      - Upjohn, 1981 (Box 13-21)
      - Upjohn, 1980 (Box 13-21)
      - Upjohn, 1979 (Box 13-21)
      - Vehicles, 1977 January-1981 December (Box 13-21)
      - Vehicle Assignment List, 1978 May-1981 December (Box 13-21)
      - Vernon, Town of, 1981 September-1981 October (Box 13-21)
      - Viking Wire Plant, 1980 July (Box 13-21)
      - Voluntown, Town of, 1980 May-1980 December (Box 13-21)
      - Wallingford, Town of, 1980 May-1981 June (Box 13-21)
      - Water Compliance Unit, 1980-1981 (Box 13-21)
      - Water Compliance Unit, 1977, 1978, 1979 (Box 13-21)
      - Water Conservation, 1981 (Box 13-21)
      - Water Monitoring, 1980 January-1981 June (Box 13-21)
      - Water Pollution, 1977 January-1980 January (Box 13-21)
      - Water Pollution Control, 1977 May-1981 June (Box 13-21)
      - Water Quality (Box 13-21)
      - Water, Research and Technology, 1976-1977-1978 (Box 13-21)
      - Water Resources, 1981-1980 (Box 13-21)
      - Water Resources, 1979 June-1979 October (Box 13-21)
      - Water Resources, 1964 February-1978 June (Box 13-21)
      - Water Resources Council, 1978-1980 (Box 13-21)
      - Water and Waste Management Book, 1978 (Box 13-21)
      - Chronological File, 1977-1980
        - 1977 April 1-30 (Box 13-22)
        - 1977 March 1-31 (Box 13-22)
        - 1977 January 1-31, February (Box 13-22)
        - 1976 August 1-November 1 (Box 13-22)
        - 1976 June 1 (Box 13-22)
        - 1976 March 11-May 28, 1976 May 31 (Box 13-22)
        - 1976 January 2-March 10 (Box 13-22)
        - 1975 November 1-December 31 (Box 13-22)
        - 1975 August 1-October 31 (Box 13-22)
        - 1975 July 1-31 (Box 13-22)
        - 1975 March 1-May 31 (Box 13-22)
        - 1979 August-December (Box 13-22)
        - 1979 January-July (Box 13-22)
        - 1978 September-December (Box 13-22)
        - 1978 May-August (Box 13-22)
        - 1978 January-April (Box 13-22)
        - 1977 October-December (Box 13-22)
        - 1977 August-September (Box 13-22)
        - 1977 June-July (Box 13-23)
        - 1980 January-June (Box 13-23)
        - 1980 July-December (Box 13-23)
    - Subject Files, 1974-1981; 1988-027 (part)
      - Legislation-Correspondence Session, 1974 (Box 23-1)
      - Legislation-Proposed Legislation (EQ), 1977 (Box 23-1)
      - Legislation-C&P Proposed Legislation, 1977 (Box 23-1)
      - Governor’s Office, 1979 December (Box 23-1)
      - Governor’s Office, 1979 September-November (Box 23-1)
      - Governor’s Office, 1979 January-February (Box 23-1)
      - Governor’s Office, 1979 march-April (Box 23-1)
      - Governor’s Office, 1979 May-June (Box 23-1)
      - Governor’s Office, 1979 July-August (Box 23-1)
      - CPTA, 1978 (Box 23-1)
      - CPTA, 1977 (Box 23-1)
      - Railroads, 1977 (Box 23-1)
      - Railroads, 1978-1979 (Box 23-1)
      - Tri-State, 1976 January-February (Box 23-2)
      - Tri-State, 1976 March-April (Box 23-2)
      - Tri-State, 1976 July-August (Box 23-2)
      - Tri-State, 1976 September-October (Box 23-2)
      - Tri-State, 1976 November-December (Box 23-2)
      - Tri-State, 1977 January-March (Box 23-2)
      - Tri-State, 1977 April-June (Box 23-2)
      - Tri-State, 1977 July-September (Box 23-2)
      - Tri-State, 1977 October-November (Box 23-2)
      - Tri-State, 1978 February-April (Box 23-2)
      - Tri-State, 1977 December-January (Box 23-2)
      - Tri-State, 1978 May-July (Box 23-2)
      - Affirmative Action, 1977-1978 (Box 23-3)
      - Air Compliance Unit, 1977 (Box 23-3)
      - Air Compliance Unit, 1978 (Box 23-3)
      - EQ Air Compliance, 1976 (Box 23-3)
      - New England River Basins, 1978 January-June (Box 23-3)
      - PFEC (Box 23-3)
      - PFEC, 1977 June-1977 November (Box 23-3)
      - PFEC, 1977 November-1978 February (Box 23-3)
      - Task Force-Railroad, 1977 (Box 23-3)
      - CRRA, 1978 November-1979 January (Box 23-4)
      - CRRA, 1978 September-October (Box 23-4)
      - CRRA, 1978 July-August (Box 23-4)
      - CRRA, 1978 February-June (Box 23-4)
      - CRRA, 1977 December-1978 January (Box 23-4)
      - CRRA, 1977 October-November (Box 23-4)
      - CRRA, 1977 August-September (Box 23-4)
      - CRRA, 1977 June-July (Box 23-4)
      - CRRA, 1977 April-May (Box 23-4)
      - CRRA, 1977 March (Box 23-4)
      - CRRA, 1977 January-February (Box 23-4)
      - CRRA files, 1976 (Box 23-4)
      - Governor’s Correspondence, 1980 July (Box 23-5)
      - CT Railway Advisory Task Force, 1977 (Box 23-5)
      - CT Railway Advisory Task Force (Box 23-5)
      - CEPA (Box 23-5)
      - Planning and Coordination, 1978 (Box 23-6)
      - Public Utilities Control Authority (Box 23-6)
      - PREC, 1978 March-1979 August (Box 23-6)
      - Legislation-Correspondence, 1978 Session (Box 23-6)
      - Proposed Legislation, 1979 (Box 23-6)
      - Public/Special Acts (Box 23-6)
      - Qualifications and Experience record (Box 23-6)
      - Legislator’s Program-Rules and Regulations Committee (Box 23-6)
      - Rail, 1980 January (Box 23-7)
      - Rail, 1980 August (Box 23-7)
      - Rail, 1980 September (Box 23-7)
      - Rail, 1981 January-February (Box 23-7)
      - Appointments made by Governor, 1976 January-June (Box 23-7)
      - Appointments made by Governor, 1975-1976 (Box 23-7)
      - Miscellaneous Inquires from Governor’s Office (Box 23-7)
      - Governor’s File (Box 23-7)
      - Cam, 1977-1978 (Box 23-7)
      - DOT, 1979 (Box 23-7)
      - Energy Planning (Box 23-7)
      - 208 Water (Box 23-7)
      - 208 Water, 1977-1979 (Box 23-7)
      - Water Resources Development in Connecticut (Box 23-7)
      - Water Resources Council Policy Study, 1977-1979 (Box 23-7)
      - Wildlife, 1979 (Box 23-7)
      - Governor’s Correspondence, 1976 March-April (Box 23-8)
      - Governor’s Correspondence (Box 23-8)
      - Governor’s Correspondence, 1977 January-February (Box 23-8)
      - Governor’s Correspondence, 1977 May-June (Box 23-8)
      - Governor’s Correspondence, 1977 July-August (Box 23-8)
      - Governor’s Correspondence, 1977 September-October (Box 23-8)
      - Governor’s Correspondence, 1978 November-December (Box 23-8)
      - Governor’s Correspondence, 1979 September-October (Box 23-8)
      - Governor’s Correspondence, 1979 July-August (Box 23-8)
      - Governor’s Correspondence, 1979 May-June (Box 23-8)
      - Governor’s Correspondence, 1978 January-February (Box 23-8)
    - Subject Files, 1977-1980; 1988-030
      - Affirmative Action Update, 1979 (Box 28-1)
      - Attorney General, 1978 (Box 28-1)
      - Bond Requests, 1977 (Box 28-1)
      - Bond Requests, 1978 (Box 28-1)
      - Bond Requests, 1979 (Box 28-1)
      - Air Compliance, 1979 (Box 28-1)
      - CT Air Quality Summary (Box 28-1)
      - Commissioner Pac-Personal, 1977 (Box 28-1)
      - CAM, 1979 (Box 28-1)
      - CPTA, 1979 (Box 28-1)
      - Hazardous Materials Management Unit, 1978 (Box 28-2)
      - Hazardous Materials Management Unit, 1979 (Box 28-2)
      - Hazardous Waste-CT Industrial Waste Management and Recovery Task Force (Box 28-2)
      - HCRS (Box 28-2)
      - Human Resources-DAS (Box 28-2)
      - Staff Services (Box 28-2)
      - Inspection and Maintenance (Box 28-2)
      - Air Compliance Unit-Indirect Sources (Box 28-2)
      - Energy, 1977 (Box 28-3)
      - Energy, 1978 (Box 28-3)
      - CRRA, 1979 February-1979 March (Box 28-3)
      - CRRA, 1979 April-1979 May (Box 28-3)
      - CRRA, 1979 June-1979 July (Box 28-3)
      - CRRA, 1979 August-1979 (Box 28-3)
      - CRRA, 1979 October-1979 November (Box 28-3)
      - Environmental Quality, 1977 (Box 28-3)
      - Governor’s Office, 1980 January (Box 28-3)